<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="peripheral.joystick"
  version="20.1.3"
  name="Joystick Support"
  provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" minversion="2.0.0" version="2.0.2"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" minversion="1.0.4" version="1.0.5"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" minversion="1.1.7" version="1.1.7"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.tools" minversion="1.0.0" version="1.0.4"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.instance.peripheral" minversion="2.0.0" version="2.0.0"/></requires>
  <extension
    point="kodi.peripheral"
    provides_joysticks="true"
    provides_buttonmaps="true"
    library_windowsstore="peripheral.joystick.dll"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/peripheral.joystick</source>
    <platform></platform>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Llibreria Kodi Joystick</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Kodi Joystick Bibliotek</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Joystick-Bibliothek für Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi Joystick Library</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Librería Kodi Joystick</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Biblioteca de Joysticks de Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Kodin peliohjainkirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Bibliothèque de joystick Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Kodi Joystick biblioteka</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Libreria Joystick Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Kodi 조이스틱 라이브러리</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Kodi kursorsviru katalogs</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Kodi Joystick-bibliotek</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Biblioteka joysticków Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Biblioteca de Joystick do Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Biblioteca de joysticks do Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Каталог джойстиков для Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Kodi Joystick bibliotek</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Kodi Oyun Çubuğu Kütüphanesi</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Kodi 游戏杆库</summary>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquesta llibreria proporciona controladors de joystick i mapes de botons. S&apos;admeten diverses API de joystick, incloses DirectX, XInput, SDL i l&apos;API Joystick de Linux.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Dette bibliotek indeholder joystick-drivere og knapgrupperinger. Flere joystick-API&apos;er understøttes, herunder DirectX, XInput, SDL og Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Diese Bibliothek enthält Joystick-Treiber und Schaltflächenzuordnungen. Es werden mehrere Joystick-APIs unterstützt, darunter DirectX, XInput, SDL und die Linux-Joystick-API.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This library provides joystick drivers and button maps. Multiple joystick APIs are supported, including DirectX, XInput, SDL and the Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Esta librería otorga drivers de joystick y mapeo de botones. Soporta múltiples APIs de joystick, incluyendo DirectX, XInput, SDL y la API de Joystick de Linux.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Esta biblioteca provee controladores de joysticks y mapas de botones. Múltiples APIs de joystick están soportadas, incluyendo DirectX, XInput, SDL y la Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tämä kirjasto sisältää peliohjaimien ajureita ja painikemäärtiyksiä. Useita ohjainrajapintoja tuetaan, kuten mm. DirectX, XInput, SDL ja Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Cette bibliothèque fournit des pilotes de joystick et les maps de boutons. Plusieurs API de joystick sont prises en charge, notamment DirectX, XInput, SDL et l’API Linux Joystick.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Ova biblioteka omogućuje upravljačke programe igračih palica i mapiranje tipki. Više API igračih palica je podržano, uključujući DirectX, XInput, SDL i Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questa libreria fornisce i driver del joystick e le mappe dei pulsanti. Sono supportate più API joystick, tra cui DirectX, XInput, SDL e l&apos;API Joystick Linux.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">이 라이브러리는 조이스틱 드라이버와 버튼 맵을 제공합니다. DirectX, XInput, SDL 및 Linux Joystick API를 비롯한 여러 조이스틱 API가 지원됩니다.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Šajā katalogā ir pieejami kursorsviras draiveri un pogu izkārtojuma kartes. Tiek atbalstītas vairākas kursorsviras API, tostarp DirectX, XInput, SDL un Linux kursorsviras API.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Dette biblioteket inneholder joystick-drivere og knappkartlegging. Flere joystick-APIer støttes, blant annet DirectX, XInput, SDL og Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Ta biblioteka zawiera sterowniki joysticków i mapy przycisków. Obsługiwanych jest wiele interfejsów API joysticków, m.in. DirectX, XInput, SDL oraz Joystick API systemu Linux.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Esta biblioteca fornece drivers de joystick e mapeamento de botões. Diversas APIs de joystick são suportadas, incluindo DirectX, XInput, SDL e API de Joystick do Linux.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Esta biblioteca fornece controladores de joystick e mapeamentos de botões. São suportadas múltiplas APIs de joystick, incluindo DirectX, XInput, SDL e a API do joystick para Linux.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Этот каталог предоставляет драйверы джойстиков и схемы расположения кнопок. Поддерживается несколько API джойстиков, включая DirectX, XInput, SDL и Linux Joystick API.</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Bu kitaplık, oyun çubuğu sürücüleri ve düğme haritaları sağlar. DirectX, XInput, SDL ve Linux Oyun Çubuğu API dahil olmak üzere çoklu oyun çubuğu API&apos;leri desteklenir.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">此库提供游戏杆驱动程序和按钮图。支持多个游戏杆 API，包括 DirectX、XInput、SDL 和 Linux 游戏杆 API。</description>
  </extension>
</addon>
